Jojo Betzler.
Ten years old.
Today, you join the ranks
of the Jungvolk
in a very special
training weekend.
It's going to be intense.
But today, you become a man.
I swear to devote all
my energies and my strength
to the savior of our country,
Adolf Hitler.
I am willing and ready
to give up my life for him.
So help me God.
Yes, that's right.
- Now, Jojo Betzler, what is your mind?
- Snake mind.
- And, Jojo Betzler, what is your body?
- Wolf body.
- Jojo Betzler, what is your courage?
- Panther courage.
- And, Jojo Betzler, what is your soul?
- A German soul.
Yeah, man. You're ready.
- Adolf.
- Hmm?
I don't think I can do this.
Was?
Of course you can.
Sure, you're a little bit
scrawny and a bit unpopular
and you can't tie your
shoelaces even though you're ten years old
But you're still the bestest,
most loyal little Nazi I've ever met.
Not to mention the fact
you're really good-looking.
So, you're gonna get out there
and you're gonna have a great time, okay?
- Okay.
- That's the spirit. Okay.
Heil me, man.
Heil Hitler.
What? You can heil me
better than that.
- Heil Hitler.
- No...
Just throw it away.
Don't even think about it.
- Heil Hitler.
- No, you're overthinking it.
- Heil "Hitterler."
Who's "Hitterler?"
Do you even speak German?
-  Heil Hitler.
- That's not a heil.
This is a heil. Heil!
- Heil Hitler! Heil Hitler.
- Heil Hitler. Heil Hitler!
- Heil Hitler.
- Heil Hitler! Heil Hitler!
Ooh, that's it.
You've got it. Heil Hitler.
- Have a great day! You're gonna be the best.
- Heil Hitler! Heil Hitler!
- Heil Hitler! You can do it.
Heil Hitler! Heil Hitler!
Heil Hitler!
Whoa!
-♪ Oh, komm doch,
komm zu mir ♪
- Heil Hitler.
-♪ Du nimmst
mir der Verstand ♪
- Heil Hitler. Heil Hitler.
♪ Oh, komm doch, komm zu mir ♪
♪ Komm, gib mir deine Hand ♪
♪ Komm,
gib mir deine Hand ♪
♪ Komm, gib mir deine Hand ♪
♪ Oh, du bist so schön ♪
♪ Schön wie ein Diamant ♪
Heil Hitler. Heil Hitler.
-♪ Ich will mit dir gehen ♪
- Heil Hitler. Heil Hitler.
Heil Hitler. Heil Hitler.
♪ Komm, gib mir deine Hand ♪
- Heil Hitler, Yorki.
- Heil Hitler, Jojo.
- Are you ready for
the best weekend ever?
- Yes, I am.
Let's go.
♪ Das war noch nie
bei einer Anderen ♪
- ♪ Einmal so,
Einmal so ♪
♪ Einmal so ♪
♪ Oh, du bist so schön ♪
♪ Schön wie ein Diamant ♪
♪ Ich will mit dir gehen ♪
♪ Komm, gib mir deine Hand ♪
♪ Komm,
gib mir deine Hand ♪
♪ Komm, gib mir deine Hand ♪
♪ Komm,
gib mir deine Hand ♪
Heil! Heil! Heil!
Heil Hitler, guys.
Heil Hitler!
Jungvolk, welcome to
the Hitlerjugend
training weekend.
In which we will make
men and women of you all.
My name is Captain Klenzendorf.
You may call me Captain K.
Captain K. Whoo!
Ja. And this is
Sub-Officer Finkel.
This is Fräulein Rahm.
Hey. Heil Hitler, everyone.
So a little about me.
Who am I?
And why am I here
talking to a bunch
of little titty-grabbers
instead of leading my men
into battle towards glorious
death? Great question.
I've asked it myself every day
since Operation Screw Up
where I lost a perfectly
good eye in a totally
preventable enemy attack.
And according to my superiors,
you need two eyes
to be a meaningful part
of the war effort.
Can two-eyed people do this?
- Jesus.
- Over the next two days,
you little critters
will get to experience
some of the things
that the mighty German army
goes through every day.
And even though
it would appear
our country's on the back foot
and there really isn't much
hope in us winning this war,
apparently
we're doing just fine.
Anyway. You boys have
all been issued with your
Deutsches Jungvolk daggers.
These are very special
and expensive weapons.
You should never
be without them.
And don't try to
stab each other.
No stabbing!
No stabbing.
This is your first step
towards being men.
Today you boys will be
involved in such activities
as marching, bayonet drills,
grenade-throwing,
trench-digging,
map-reading, gas defense,
camouflage, ambush techniques,
war games, firing guns,
and blowing stuff up.
The girls will practice
important womanly duties
such as dressing wounds,
making beds,
and learning how
to get pregnant.
Aw.
I've had 18 kids for Germany.
Such a great year to be a girl.
All right. Let's get to it.
Come on.
Go!
God help me.
♪ Well, when I'm lyin'
in my bed at night ♪
Go, go, go!
♪ Nothin' ever seems
to turn out right ♪
♪ I don't want to grow up ♪
Three, two, one,
swastika!
♪ How do you move
in a world of fog ♪
Come on!
Pull it! Come on!
♪ Makes me wish
that I could be a dog ♪
Aaah! Aaah!
♪ Well, when I see
the price that you pay ♪
♪ I don't ever
want to be that way ♪
♪ I don't want to grow up ♪
- Now finish him.
- Don't, no, no!
♪ The only thing
to live for is today ♪
- Fangs.
- Fangs, ja.
- Serpent tongue.
- Serpent's tongue, ja.
- Scales.
- Ja, scales.
Because, once upon a time,
a Jewish man
mated with a fish.
Whoa!
We, Aryans, are
one thousand times
more civilized and advanced
than any other race.
Now, get your
things together, kids.
It's time to burn some books.
Yeah!
♪ Comb their hair
and shine their shoes ♪
♪ I don't want to grow up ♪
♪ Stay around
my old hometown ♪
♪ I don't want to put
no money down ♪
♪ I don't want to
get me a big old loan ♪
♪ Work them fingers
to the bone ♪
♪ I don't want to
float a broom ♪
♪ Fall in love and
get married, then boom ♪
♪ How the hell
did it get here so soon? ♪
♪ I don't want to grow up ♪
Jews sound scary, huh?
Not to me.
If I met one,
I'd kill it like that.
Like... that.
But how would you know
if you saw one?
They could look just like us.
I'd feel its head for horns.
And they smell like
brussels sprouts.
Oh, yeah. I forgot about
the brussels sprouts bit.
Imagine catching one
and giving it to Hitler.
That'd be a surefire way to
get into his personal guards.
Then we would become
best friends.
I thought I was
your best friend.
Yorki, you're
my second-best friend.
First place
is reserved for the Führer.
So, unless you're Hitler
hiding in a fat,
little boy's body...
I'd be happy with second place.
I guess I'm just a kid
in a fat kid's body.
Case closed.
Raah! Raah! Raah!
When you stand
before the enemy
and have to end his life,
which of you will have
the stomach to do this?
Good.
There is no room
in Hitler's army
for those that lack strength.
We want hardened warriors.
Those that are prepared
to kill at will.
Can you do this?
- Yes.
- Ja.
Johannes.
Can you kill?
Pfff. Of course.
I love killing.
Good. Come here.
Don't be scared. Come on.
Good.
Kill it.
Huh?
Wring its neck
and kill the rabbit.
Or are you scared?
I'm not scared. I... I just...
Now.
Place both hands around its
neck and then one hard twist.
He might scream,
but we'll just use
the boot to finish it off.
Kill. Kill.
Kill. Kill. Kill.
Kill.
Kill. Kill.
Kill. Kill. Kill.
- Shoo! Come on, shoo.
- Hey! Hey, hey.
Good shot.
You are a coward.
Just like your father.
He... He's not a coward.
- He's fighting in Italy.
- Really?
But no one has heard
from him in two years.
He is a deserting coward.
He's scared and so are you.
You're as scared
as a little rabbit.
Scared little rabbit.
Maybe we should snap
your neck, too?
Jojo the rabbit.
Jojo Rabbit.
Jojo Rabbit. Jojo Rabbit.
Poor Jojo.
What's wrong, little man?
- Hi, Adolf.
- Wanna tell me about
that rabbit incident?
What was all that about?
They wanted me to kill it.
I'm sorry. I couldn't.
Don't worry about it.
I couldn't care less.
But now they call me
a scared rabbit.
Let them say whatever they want.
People used to say a lot
of nasty things about me.
"Oh, this guy's a lunatic."
"Oh, look at that psycho.
He's gonna get us all killed."
I'm gonna let you in
on a little secret.
The rabbit is no coward.
The humble little bunny faces
a dangerous world every day,
hunting carrots for
his family, for his country.
My empire will be
full of all animals.
Lions, giraffes, zebras,
rhinoceroses, octopuses,
rhinoctopuses.
Even the mighty rabbit.
Cigarette?
Oh, no, thanks. I don't smoke.
Let me give you
some really good advice.
Be the rabbit.
The humble bunny
can outwit all of his enemies.
He's brave and sneaky
and strong.
Be the rabbit.
Jojo!
Are you all right, Jojo?
Who were you talking to?
Nobody.
Oh, I thought you were crying.
Are you a teardrop specialist?
No.
Case closed.
Now, it's time for Jojo
to show those stick insects
who is the real cowardly rabbit.
I'm sorry,
what are you talking about?
Never mind.
Jojo, where are you going?
To be the rabbit!
Jojo Rabbit. Jojo Rabbit.
Hunting carrots. Jojo Rabbit.
Hey, this is amazing.
We're like two human antelopes.
Now, lads, each of you
will be given the opportunity
to ignite and throw a grenade.
I will personally
be supervising each of you
to make sure you don't blow
your eyes out or something.
All right, who's first?
Klaus.
Shit.
Shit!
Don't do that.
Jojo. Jojo.
Finkel! Finkel!
Jojo, Jojo.
O-M Gott.
He looks like
a Picasso painting.
His mother's going to kill me.
My darling cub.
Hey, kid.
Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm.
Mmm. My darling little cub.
Why so happy?
Your son is ugly like a monster.
Hey. You're no monster.
Besides, your scars will heal,
and you'll get most of the
movement back in your leg.
But I'll never be
in Hitler's personal guards.
Ah, you're fine as you are.
I'm just happy to have you
back home. Hmm?
Mama Lion worries about her cub,
especially when
Papa Lion isn't here.
Or Inge Lion.
You grab
the rabbit by the tail,
wrap it around his ear,
tie it all up and then
stuff him back down the hole.
Now then,
let's get on our way, huh?
I think getting out of
the house will do wonders
for your recuperation.
I don't want to go out there.
What? Don't be silly.
Of course you do.
I look stupid.
People will stare.
Enjoy the attention, kid.
Not everyone's
lucky enough to look stupid.
I, for one, am cursed
to look incredibly attractive.
Now, you're going to
pluck up your courage,
walk out that door and have
an incredible adventure.
Okay?
Okay.
Field Marshal Jojo,
you're our top man.
Prepare to leave the house.
Is it dangerous?
Extremely.
- Heil Hitler.
- Oh, Jesus.
Hey!
- Looking good, kid.
- Heil Hitler!
Frau Betzler, you're looking
fetching as usual.
Okay, wow.
It's because of you
my son can't walk properly
and has a messed-up face.
He stole my hand grenade.
- Just took it...
- Ja, ja.
So, you are going
to look after him
while I'm at work, hmm?
Make sure he has a job
and feels included. Got it?
Got it. Ja, I really got it.
Good.
Guys, this is Johannes Betzler.
The kid I told you about.
Remember,
he stole a hand grenade
and blew himself up
and as a result
I got demoted for negligence.
Now I get to work
in this office
with all these wonderful kids.
So, Jojo.
I'm sure we can figure out
something for you to do.
- Oh!
- Ideas?
- Ja.
- Guys?
Ja. Ja.
Okay, well, we need somebody
to walk the clones.
Also, I think maybe he could
hand out this new propaganda,
and deliver these conscriptions.
I don't suppose
I could be conscripted?
Could I?
Oh, yes,
that's a wonderful idea.
Yes, I give my full permission
for you to send this
ten-year-old child into war.
Will someone get this kid a gun?
And I'd be more than happy
to fight in the front.
Get in line, kid.
Okay. Here are
the conscriptions,
and here is a gun.
Ooh! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
It's a bit... for the gun?
No.
Yuck.
Look.
What did they do?
What they could.
Come on.
Hey-hey! Jojo Rabbit!
Oh, look at your face.
I am a soldier!
I'm going to war!
And you are a postman!
Jojo Rabbit, Jojo Rabbit!
Mama?
Field Marshal Jojo is home.
Mama? I'm home.
Mama?
Hi.
What do you want?
Are you a ghost?
Sure. A ghost.
Don't make me run, kid.
I'm far too hungry
and you know how much
we love the taste of blood.
Lose something?
I'm not a ghost, Johannes.
I'm something worse,
but I think you already
know that, don't you?
You know what I am.
- No.
- Yes.
Say it.
Say it!
A Jew.
Gesundheit.
You can't be here.
Well, your mother invited me,
so I suppose that makes me
her guest.
- It's not allowed.
- What will you do,
sweet Hitlerchen?
Hmm?
Of course.
Go on, then. Tell them.
But do you know
what happens if you do?
I'll tell them you helped me.
And your mother, too.
Then we'll all be kaputt.
And if you tell her you know
about me, just one word...
I'll do the world
a great, big favor
and cut your Nazi head off.
Got it?
Ja.
I think I'll hold onto this.
It's pretty.
Sheesh. That was intense.
- What am I going to do?
- Honestly, no idea.
I mean,
there could be more of them.
Hundreds of them
living in your walls.
How did she get control
like that?
She must've used her powers.
Mind control.
Oh, typical.
- Did you see
how fast she moved?
- Yes.
Like a little,
female Jewish Jesse Owens.
- And now she's got
your fancy knife.
- My knife!
Yeah. Like a little, female
Jewish Jesse Owens,
Jack the Ripper.
You're definitely
in a pickle, my friend.
Ah, what to do, what to do?
- Oh. Got it!
- Got it!
- I will negotiate.
- Burn down the house
and blame Winston Churchill.
Or negotiate. Hmm.
Excuse me?
Little girl?
Um... Jew girl in the wall?
Yoo-hoo. Jew?
Okay, well, I'll just say
what I have to say
and that's this:
I'm not scared of you
and I think you should find
somewhere else to live.
Okay?
Not okay.
Get the hell out of my room.
She's pretty rude, you know?
That's just my two Pfennige.
- And now she's got two knives.
- I know!
- How are you
going to chop up stuff?
- I don't know!
Oh, and she's
still up there, too.
That... that thing, that, that...
- Jew.
- Yeah. Jew, yeah.
- What are we gonna do
about that Jew?
- You think of something.
Oh, now I'm the expert?
Stop offering me
damned cigarettes! I'm ten!
All right. Sorry.
I'm stressed out!
Okay, let's talk like turkeys.
You can't tell your mother
or that Jew will cut off
your Nazi head,
but there's no reason
this thing in the attic
needs to ruin your life.
In fact, you could use it
to your advantage.
How?
When someone tries to use
mind powers on me,
know what I do?
Use mind powers back on them.
Remember last year
when that one-arm pirate
von Stauffenberg
tried to blow me up
with a table bomb?
Yeah, you survived.
Correctomundo.
The only reason I survived,
apart from having
bombproof legs,
is because I outwitted
old von Stauffy.
I let him think that I was
dead, when in actual fact,
I was absolutely fine.
By pretending I was dead,
I drew out all the traitors.
So what are you going to do?
Pretend I'm dead?
Exactly. Wait, no.
No, what I mean is this:
make her feel safe
and then she'll drop her guard
and then you will be
the one in control.
- Reverse psychology.
- Don't complicate things.
Just use my backwards
mind power trick,
and everything will be fine.
Ooh! I gotta go.
We're having
unicorn for dinner
at my place tonight.
Concentrate, Jojo.
Remember,
a Jew living in your wall
is better than
two Jews flying around
with their bat wings
climbing down chimneys
and eating innocent Nazis.
And don't give her
any more knives.
Tschüss.
Darling cub,
why are you up, huh?
Did you eat anything, hmm?
Sorry, I lost track of time.
I was taking a long walk
and having a thing...
What are we going to do
with these laces, huh?
My goodness.
You'll learn how to
tie them eventually, no?
- I heard her.
- What?
Who?
Inge.
Her ghost.
Oh. That's so sad for you.
You've lost your mind.
It's sadder for me, though,
because I have to live
with a crazy person.
I heard noises. Upstairs.
Ghosts? Honestly.
You know what I heard? Rats.
Yes, we have them.
Can you believe that?
Dirty animals.
I've been meaning to tell you
to stay away from upstairs,
until I've cleared
them all, okay?
I don't need you getting sick.
Okay, Mama.
I'll watch out
for those dirty rats.
Where are all
the goddamn knives?
Are you going to bed, too?
Yes. Soon.
I have to tidy
some things first.
What things?
Mama things.
Boy, you have to trust me, okay?
I'm the boss here, ja?
I guess.
Good boy.
Yes, but with...
with one eye. Like...
Almost.
Not quite.
Great. You got it.
Ja.
You have to be more quiet.
He heard noises up here.
If I have to choose
between you and my son, I...
I won't know where to send you.
You hear me?
He can't know.
If he knows, then they know.
- You could reason with him.
- You don't know him.
He's a fanatic.
It took him three weeks
to get over the fact
that his grandfather
was not blond.
I know he's in there somewhere.
The little boy who loves to
play and runs to you
because he's scared of thunder.
Thinks you invented
chocolate cake.
In the end, that's all you have.
Hope...
that your only remaining child
is not just another ghost.
Perhaps we're all ghosts now.
We just don't know it.
Perhaps.
You've lived
more lifetimes than most.
I haven't lived at all.
You're being challenged.
They say you can't live,
that you won't live.
If that comes true,
then they win.
They've been winning so far.
They'll never win.
That's the power you have.
As long as
there's someone alive,
somewhere, then they lose.
They didn't get you
yesterday or today.
You make tomorrow the same.
Hey.
Tomorrow must be the same.
Jesus Christ!
You must stretch.
Does that hurt you?
- Yes.
- Good. Pain is your friend.
Soon your leg will only be
a little bit deformed
and pointless.
I'm going to recommend another
month off school though
because your face
might scare the other kids.
It's kind of ugly.
Okay, who's next?
Jojo.
Baby, I have to go.
I'll see you at home. Mmm.
- Hi, Captain K.
- Hey.
If it isn't
Herr Hand Grenade himself.
Ah.
How's the leg, kid?
It's pretty much healed.
It only 80% hurts now.
What are you guys doing?
I'm being made
to teach the HJ boys
water warfare training.
You know, in case they ever need
to go to battle
in a swimming pool.
Can I ask you
a question about Jews?
Oh, God. Why?
What should I do if I see one?
Ugh. Okay.
If you see a Jew, you tell us,
we tell the Gestapo,
and they tell the SS,
and then they go
and they kill the Jew.
And anyone who helped the Jew.
And because these are very
paranoid times,
probably some
other people just in case.
It's a pretty drawn out process.
Even if the Jew
hypnotized someone
to make them hide
the Jew in the first place?
I'd be amazed
if that could happen.
No, it can happen.
It happened to my uncle.
A Jew hypnotized him
and he became a massive
drunk and a gambler.
And he cheated on his wife
and he had an inappropriate
relationship with my sister.
And then he drowned
in an unrelated accident,
but it was the Jew's fault.
Anyway. Did you see one?
A Jew.
- I'm not sure I'd be able
to tell if I did.
Yeah, me neither.
Without their funny hats,
it's damn near impossible.
Someone should write a book
on the subject.
It would make things
so much easier.
- It would be a hit.
- Ja.
Finkie, they're drowning.
Come on.
I'll see you later, little man.
Okay, here's the situation.
If I tell on you,
you'll be in big trouble,
and I don't think you want that.
But then you'll tell on me
and my mother,
and we'll be in trouble,
which I don't want.
And if you
tell my mother I know,
then she'll kick you out,
which you don't want.
And if I tell my mother I know,
then you'll
cut off my Nazi head,
which I also don't want.
So, it's a Mexican stalemate.
It's just a normal stalemate.
I have some conditions
for allowing you to stay here.
- "Conditions?"
- Yes.
Tell me everything
about the Jewish race.
Okay.
We're like you,
but human.
Please take this seriously.
Think of this as an exposé.
I want to know all your secrets.
Kindly refrain from sitting
on my sister's bed.
Why? She doesn't need it.
You know nothing of my sister.
Inge and I were friends.
I remember you.
Such a funny little boy.
Enough with the small talk.
Start telling me
about your kind.
Obviously, we are demons
who love money.
Right?
Obviously.
Everyone knows that.
But what people don't know
is that we're also allergic
to food.
Cheese, bread, meat.
That stuff
will kill us instantly.
So, if you're thinking
of ending my life,
that's the fastest way.
Also biscuits, lethal.
Very funny.
Anyway, there's not enough
food for you,
so I don't know
what you're going to do.
Your mother managed
to find me some bread.
She's kind.
She treats me like a person.
But you're not.
Not a proper person.
Are you?
How dare you, Jew!
You are weak like an eyelash.
I am born of Aryan ancestry.
My blood is the color
of a pure red rose.
And my eyes are blue like...
Break free.
Break free, great Aryan.
There are no weak Jews.
I am descended
from those who wrestle angels
and kill giants.
We were chosen by God.
You were chosen by a
pathetic little man
who can't even grow
a full mustache.
The stronger race, huh?
So, how's it all going
with that Jew thing upstairs?
Well, she doesn't want
to talk to me.
Mm-hmm. Well, you are a Nazi.
I guess.
This book is going
to be harder to write
than I thought.
Hmm.
- What's she doing?
- She's burning something.
What is she burning?
What are you burning?
She can't hear you.
Why so happy?
Things are changing.
The Allies have taken Italy.
France will be next
and soon the war will be over.
Goddamn it!
Why does that make you happy?
You hate your country that much?
I love my country.
It's the war I hate.
It's pointless and stupid,
and the sooner
we have peace, the better.
Oh, the war will end.
We will crush our enemies
into dust.
And when they are destroyed,
we shall use
their graves as toilets.
Okay. No more politics.
Dinner is neutral ground.
This table is Switzerland.
Let's eat.
You aren't eating.
No. I am not that hungry.
I might eat later.
For now, I am just going to
chew on these grapes.
Well, I'm especially hungry
tonight.
So maybe I'll just finish yours.
Don't want it to go to waste.
How was your day, Johannes?
Oh, you know,
just wandered around,
being a deformed kid
with nothing to live for.
You're not deformed.
My face looks like
a goddamn street map, woman.
I wouldn't expect you
to understand.
If my father were here,
he'd get it.
Well, he's not.
I know. And instead,
I'm stuck with you.
You want your dad, 'eh?
Yeah, I do.
- Yeah? Yeah?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Yeah!
Fine.
Don't you ever talk
to your goddamn mother
like that!
Paul, what happened?
Paul?
I yelled at the kid.
What? Go apologize.
Sorry, kid.
What?
What kind of apology was that?
Sorry, kid.
Jojo...
I know you miss me, but I'm...
I'm out there
trying to make
a difference in the world.
And while I'm gone,
I need you
to take care of my Rosie.
Can you do that?
Yes, Dad.
Thanks.
She's doing what she can.
Oh, gosh.
We made a good kid, huh?
Mm-mm! Damn, that's good.
It reminds me of dancing
with Rosie in The Red Salon.
You remember, honey?
Of course I do, babe.
Hey, don't just
sit there, kid.
Come.
Dance with your parents, come.
So, I'd like you to draw
a picture of where Jews live.
Where you all eat, sleep,
and where the queen Jew
lays the eggs.
You really are an idiot.
Come on. We have
a lot of work to do.
Tell me about your family.
I'll tell you about the Jews,
but you are not privileged
to know about my family.
But I need background.
Why are you
hanging around with me?
Don't you have any friends?
Of course. Yorki.
- "Yorki?"
- Amongst others.
Well, you don't have anyone.
I have Nathan.
"Nathan?"
Who the hell is that?
- My fiancé. I have him.
- Where is he?
Fighting in the resistance, see.
He proposed to me
on the banks of the Fluß.
He knelt down
like a proper gentleman,
recited a poem by Rilke.
And when I said yes,
we danced into the night.
Snore.
Who's Rilke?
A great poet.
Nathan's favorite.
Oh, Nathan's favorite? Yay.
He's coming to rescue me,
then we'll go live in Paris.
You'd turn your back
on Germany forever?
It turned on me first.
Well, we don't need you.
You and your stupid boyfriend
can shut up
and go live in damn
cheese, snail, baguette land.
Now, now, just because
you don't have a girlfriend.
I'm way too busy
for a girlfriend.
One day, you'll make time.
You'll think of nothing else.
You'll meet someone
and spend your days
dreaming of the moment you can
hold them in your arms again.
That's love.
- Ridiculous.
- Finished.
I said to draw where Jews live.
This is just a stupid picture
of my head.
Yeah. That's where we live.
Rilke, Rilke, Rilke.
Where are you?
Poetry-writing dumbhead.
Ah.
Yes. Great thinking, Rabbit.
We'll use all of these books
to make a fake floor
that she'll fall through.
Straight into
a pit full of piranhas
and... and lava and bacon.
- Why, she won't know
what hit her.
- Shh!
- Shh?
You shush. Shush me?
Let's get a book and let's go.
Libraries are dumb.
Yeah,
this is a really good idea,
what we're doing right now.
If she had a heart, this would
break it clean in two.
I have something to tell you.
I came across
an old letter from Nathan,
your fiancé, addressed to you.
- What the hell
are you talking about?
- I'll just read it.
"Dear Elsa, this is hard
for me to say,
"but I don't want
to marry you anymore.
"I found a new woman
and we laugh a lot
"and do the tongue-kiss.
"It's like my favorite poet,
Rilke, says,
"'We need in love
to practice only this:
letting each other go.'
"So, goodbye and sorry
about letting you go.
"From Nathan, your ex-fiancé.
"PS, I'm not really
in the resistance.
"I was lying.
I'm unemployed
and quite fat now."
Um... don't open the door,
but I actually forgot
there was a second letter.
"Dear Elsa...
"I just wanted
to let you know that I don't
want to break up with you now.
"I changed my mind
because I don't want you
to kill yourself over me,
"which a couple of girls
have done in the past,
"and it's pretty stressful.
"I need you to stay alive.
"Thank God you're being
taken care of by that kid
"who I must say is
a remarkable young man
beyond his years.
"And brave, too.
"And let's still
get married sometime,
"even though
I am truly unemployed
"and have nothing
going on for me.
Yours, Nathan."
- Beethoven.
- Einstein.
- Bach.
- Gershwin.
Brahms. Wagner. Mozart.
Musicians, is that all you have?
Rilke.
Oh, yeah, of course.
Your favorite, Rilke.
Jewish mother.
Dietrich, then.
Houdini.
- No. That's impossible.
- Believe it, brother.
Just ask Pissarro, Modigliani,
Man Ray, Gertrude Stein,
Mr. Moses
and the king of them all,
Jesus Christi. Amen.
Pew, pew, pew!
Well, you're just saying
any old name now.
I've never heard
of these people
and now I'm fed up.
Hey.
If you find any more
of those letters,
will you let me know?
Sure.
Okay.
Bye.
Ah, these banks
used to be full of lovers.
There was dancing and singing.
Romance.
There's no time for romance.
We're at war.
Oh. There's always time
for romance.
Someday you'll meet
someone special.
Why does everyone
keep telling me that?
Who else tells you that?
Everyone.
Anyway.
It's a stupid idea.
You're stupid.
Love is the strongest thing
in the world.
I think you'll find that metal
is the strongest thing
in the world.
Followed closely by dynamite,
and then muscles.
Besides, I wouldn't
even know it if I saw it.
Surprise, surprise.
Your shoelaces are undone again.
Oh, Jojo.
You'll know when it happens.
You'll feel it.
It's a pain.
- In my arse, I bet.
- In your tummy.
Like, like, you're
full of butterflies.
- Yuck.
- Yeah, "yuck."
Come on, Shitler.
Let's get a move on.
Whoa!
- Hey!
- What's wrong with you?
I'm worried about you, man.
Are you drunk? Again?
Come on. Oh, God.
Could you
please untie them?
- You're really getting fat.
- I'm not...
You know what? Why don't I
just leave you here, okay?
- No.
- I'll come and
get you tomorrow.
- Okay? How about that?
- No. Mama, Mama!
You'll figure it out, darling.
- No!
- I'll meet you
back at the house.
- I'll see you
tomorrow morning.
- Mama, Mama!
You're growing up too fast.
Ten-year-olds
shouldn't be celebrating war
and talking politics.
You should be climbing trees
and then falling out of
those trees.
But the Führer says when we win
it is us, young boys
who will rule the world.
Pfft!
The Reich is dying.
We're going to lose the war
and then what are you
going to do, hmm?
Life is a gift.
We must celebrate it.
We have to dance to show God
we are grateful to be alive.
Well, I won't dance.
Dancing is for people
who don't have a job.
who are free.
It's an escape from all this.
Well, you're free
to dance your way home.
I'll ride.
Oh, no, you don't.
No one can stop me.
Welcome home, boys!
Now, go home
and kiss your mothers!
No news from Nathan today,
I'm afraid.
He's probably doing
something amazing,
like reading a book
or growing a beard.
What's wrong?
You want me to tell you
about the Jews?
Don't care.
In the beginning,
we used to live in caves.
- Deep, deep
in the center of the Earth.
- Wait.
Scary places full of strange
and wonderful creatures
all with one thing in common.
Mm-hmm. Stealing
the ends of penises?
No, you idiot.
- The love of art.
- No cutting penises off?
Do you want the story or not?
You may continue,
but I know it's true.
The penis thing.
Rabbis use them for earplugs.
And moving on.
After many years of developing
magic and spells,
we slowly moved out of
the caves and into the towns.
Some of us
stayed in the caves,
though, in animal bodies.
Which are blobs or something?
Well, I'll draw them for you.
There.
It'd be better with color.
Where's the horns?
Under the hair.
Where's yours?
I'm too young.
- They grow when you turn 21.
- Oh.
These days we live
among normal people,
but often we take over a house
and hang from
the ceiling when we sleep.
Like bats.
Oh, and another thing is
we can read each other's minds.
Oh, my God.
Everyone's minds?
- What about German minds?
- No.
Their heads are too thick
for us to penetrate.
Like birds, our true language
sounds like singing.
And we're also attracted
to shiny things.
Crystals, glass and gold.
"Attracted to shiny things."
But also ugly things.
Jews love ugliness.
That's another thing
we learned at school.
You love them, yes?
Ugly things.
Hi.
You two seem to be
getting on well.
I was just making sure
she was still alive.
- What do you care?
- I don't.
I just don't want
a dead person in my house.
- How would you like it?
- I'd love it.
More dead people
in my house, please.
Look, just all the time
you two are spending together,
it's making me feel
very uncomfortable.
You suggested it
in the first place.
Did I?
- Yeah.
- Oh, yeah, I did.
Besides, it's for the book.
Oh, God, you're right.
I'm sorry.
Did I make it weird?
It's weird now, isn't it?
It shouldn't be weird
between us.
None of this should be weird.
It's fine. I'm just tired.
I'm going to bed.
Ja, I was just keeping
your bed warm for you.
'Cause that's
what real friends do.
Hey, what do think
about this uniform?
I'm not sure
about the hips on the pants.
Should they be bigger?
- You look great.
- Thank you.
Now, listen, Jojo.
Can I give you
some really good advice?
When you see what's in her mind
and where she's trying
to make you go in your mind,
in your mind,
you must go the other way.
Get what I'm saying?
Do not let her put you
in a brain prison.
That, dear Jojo,
is one thing that cannot
and must not ever,
ever happen to a German!
Do not let your German brain
be bossed around!
I won't let her boss
my German brain around,
mein Führer.
Try not to.
Now, I think you've got
a lot of good information
in your book.
It's time to show it
to the world, don't you think?
Ja.
- Adolf?
- Hmm?
Do you think I'm ugly?
Yes.
Is he asleep?
Mmm.
He's different.
He suspects something.
He thinks Inge's ghost
lives up here.
You remind me of her.
You really do.
I would love to have seen her
grow into a woman.
But I'll have to
watch you instead.
I don't know anything
about being a woman.
Is that what it is?
You do things like drink wine?
Sure. You drink.
Champagne, if you're happy.
Champagne, if you're sad.
You drive a car.
Gamble if you want.
Own diamonds.
Learn how to fire a gun.
You travel to Morocco.
Take up lovers.
Make them suffer.
You look a tiger in the eye.
And trust without fear.
That's what it is to be a woman.
How do you do that?
How do you know
you can trust someone?
You trust them.
Good night.
All those other things.
Did you do that stuff?
You know,
go to Morocco and the rest?
No.
I never looked a tiger
in the eye.
Finkel, I meant we'd need dogs
for when the city is attacked,
not actual German shepherds.
Get them out of here.
Get them out of here!
- Now! Now! Now!
- Move along, please.
Move along, please.
Thank you, thank you.
- I'm sorry for yelling at you.
- I feel so stupid.
No, no.
It's a silly name for a dog.
I should've been more clear.
- You're doing a great job.
- Danke.
Hiya, kid.
How can we help you today,
Master Betzler?
What's up? Walk with me.
If someone turned in a Jew,
would they get a medal
or something?
Jews, Jews, Jews.
You're still going on
about those people?
You know I'm preparing the city
for imminent invasion, right?
I'm trying to plan
a defense strategy.
I've got Americans to the west,
got Russians to the east.
My friend once met some
Russians and they ate him.
Who's the walnuts?
Walnuts are just walnuts, kid.
What do you want to talk about?
Well, I am learning
a lot about Jews.
Did you know Jews
can read each other's minds?
And when they sleep,
they hang from the ceiling,
like bats.
That's fascinating.
And where did you
come by this information?
Research.
I'm writing a book.
Oh, congratulations.
What's it called?
Yoohoo Jew.
It's an exposé on Jews.
You could also call it
Who Are You, Jew?
Or what about Jews News?
Oh, you do have a wonderful
imagination on you.
- But it's real.
- Ja, of course it's real.
When I was your age,
I had an imaginary friend
called Conny.
He used to wet my bed
when I was asleep.
He got me in so much trouble.
Hey, come here.
You might like to check out
what I'm working on.
As part of our preparations
for the invasion,
I'm redesigning my uniform.
Note, the feathers
for aerodynamics,
the sparkly color
to dazzle the enemy,
the boots purely decorative.
And this,
this is a Gatling gun
mounted with a radio
which emits annoying music
to dishearten the enemy.
This is all copyrighted,
by the way.
That means you can't copy it.
Ja. Don't get any ideas, kid.
The kids tell me that
your father's away fighting.
So it appears you are now
the man of the house.
How's that going?
It's okay.
Ja?
So, what jobs
do you have for me today?
Well, I've got one, I won't lie.
It's a bit of a step down
from what you're used to,
but we need all hands on deck
right now.
Metal for Hitler!
Pots and pans
for the war effort!
♪ Here comes the metal man ♪
♪ Looking for
your pots and pans ♪
- Metal for Hitler!
Nuts and bolts!
Pots and pans!
"Free Germany."
Jojo?
- Yorki?
- Hi!
You're a soldier now?
At your service.
But you're only 11.
I know.
- May I?
- Yeah, sure.
Is that paper?
That's what
I thought at first, too,
but it's "paper-like."
It's the latest material
invented by our top scientists.
Well, I'm impressed.
Hey, Yorki.
I caught a Jew. A real one.
Oh, a Jew?
I saw some that they caught
hiding in the forest last month.
Personally, I didn't see
what all the fuss was about.
They weren't at all scary
and seemed kind of normal.
Oh, I'm getting distracted.
I got to go.
Bye.
- Bye.
- Oh, my God.
It's so hard to run
in this thing.
I found these.
You can have them.
They're probably broken.
Doesn't mean anything.
Maybe you can draw something
for my book.
I could draw you again.
No one wants to see
pictures of cripples.
You're hardly a cripple.
Besides, true artists
don't see that stuff.
Blind artists, you mean.
It's fine.
I'll just accept I'll be
one of those guys
who'll never get to kiss a girl.
You will be kissed, Jojo.
Do you want me to kiss you?
Okay.
Two things.
Thing number one:
It's illegal
for Nazis and Jews
to hang out like we do,
let alone kiss.
Thing number two:
It'd just be a sympathy kiss,
which doesn't count.
You're not a Nazi.
Uh, I'm massively
into swastikas,
so I think that's a pretty
good sign right there.
You're not a Nazi, Jojo.
You're a ten-year-old kid
who likes swastikas
and likes dressing up
in a funny uniform
and wants to be part of a club.
But you are not one of them.
Okay.
Let's just agree to disagree.
All right?
"Not a Nazi."
What a dirty Jew.
Come on. Hide.
Hurry. Go.
Heil Hitler.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I'm Captain Herman Deertz
of the Falkenheim Gestapo.
With me, Herr Mueller,
Herr Junker,
Herr Klum and Herr Frosch.
May we come in?
Thank you so much.
- Heil Hitler.
Hey, Jojo!
Hey, guys!
Good to see you!
My bicycle got a flat tire,
so I carried it.
- Captain Klenzendorf.
Heil Hitler.
- Heil Hitler.
You know Freddy Finkel.
So, did I miss anything?
No, no. We were just
" Heil Hitlering" the boy
and then
" Heil Hitlering" yourself
and then, of course,
" Heil Hitlering" Freddy Finkel
and now we are in the midst
of a routine inspection.
And, uh, what brings
you here, Captain?
Oh, we were just passing by
and we thought we'd drop off
some pamphlets for the boy.
He works for us.
- I see.
- Ja.
- And yourself?
- Oh, you know how it is.
Every day we take a call.
"Hello, is that the Gestapo?
I believe there's a Communist
hiding behind my fridge."
We go around to investigate.
It's just some mold.
So, not far off.
It's all part of the job.
Oh!
Now this is my kind
of little boy's bedroom.
Oh, yes.
There he is.
You and your friends
may have heard a rumor
that Hitler only has one ball.
This is nonsense.
He has four.
So, you are volunteering at
the Hitlerjugend office, yes?
Yes.
Oh, good for you.
I wish more of our young boys
had your blind fanaticism.
What on Earth
are those oafs up to?
Why don't we go upstairs
and see, yes?
Do you know
where your mother is?
No. I think she's in town.
Has she been spending
much time at home?
She is quite busy.
Is she?
Well, I'm pleased to see
that you're wearing your...
jugend uniform,
but...
where is your knife?
You must always carry
your DJ knife. Where is it?
- I left it...
- It's here.
And who might you be?
Well, who might you be?
And what are you doing
in my house?
You live here too?
I'm his sister, Inge.
Heil Hitler.
- Heil Hitler.
I did not know
you had a sister, Johannes.
Sometimes he'd prefer
if I was dead.
Isn't that right,
little Frankenstein?
Now, now.
There is no need to attack
his hideous physical deformity.
That is a war wound.
But, uh, why do you
have his knife?
I'm guarding my room because
he refuses to stay out of it.
Well, what do you
have hidden in there?
Oh, you know, girl stuff.
May I?
Naturally.
You see, we deal
with an inordinate
number of reports,
denunciations
and general investigations.
And, of course,
we are indeed interested
in problems of crime
and anti-party sentiment,
but we still have
one greater concern,
that of the "Goldilockses."
Sneaking around,
eating other people's food,
sleeping in their beds.
It really is quite rude.
I don't suppose I could
see your papers, could I?
Papers, Miss Betzler.
Quickly, please.
We don't have all day.
Yes, of course.
How old are you in this photo?
They're three years old.
I was 14.
Date of birth?
First of May.
1929.
Correct.
Thank you, Inge.
Get a new photo. You look
like a ghost in this one.
Wait.
What is...
this?
Yoohoo Jew.
Tell me, who did this?
I did.
It's an exposé on Jews.
How they think, behave, look.
It'll be a gift to the Führer.
Guys, you have to see this.
Oh, look at this one.
He has a tail.
There's one of them
hanging upside down
like a bat.
This one here, it is
a drawing of their heads.
And who is operating
the machinery of their brains?
The devil.
Ah, it's funny 'cause it's true.
Oh, look at
this little, stupid Jew.
There they are with horns.
What is this?
"Die, Nathan, die."
"Ways of killing Nathan."
Nathan being tortured by snakes.
Poked with sticks.
Being fired from a cannon
and just being called names.
Yeah.
Nathan being crushed
under the wheel
of an old-time
penny-farthing bicycle.
Who is Nathan, please?
Just some boy.
Nathan being roasted
over an open fire.
Reminds me,
we must get back and...
- You remember? Cause
we left that guy hanging up.
- Ja. Ja.
Thank you for this.
You have really made my day.
I do hope you continue with it.
And, of course,
if you see anything suspicious,
give us a ring.
Good day.
Heil Hitler.
Nice to meet you, Inge.
Stay home, Jojo.
Look after your family.
Look after this knife.
Elsa, you fooled them.
May seventh.
What?
She was born on the seventh,
not the first.
He was helping us.
They'll be back.
They'll figure out she's dead,
then I'll be dead.
Nobody really knows Inge died.
You could be her.
I'll tell Mama everything
when she gets home.
That I know you
and that we're friends.
Jew and Nazi are not friends.
Man, that was a complete bust.
You mind explaining that?
She's not...
She doesn't seem
like a bad person.
I am beginning
to question your loyalty
to myself and the party.
You call yourself a patriot?
Yet, where is the evidence?
The German soldier
was born out of necessity.
Germany depends on the passion
of these young men.
Passion and the readiness
to fall for the Fatherland
despite the futile efforts
of Allied war profiteers
who send their
ill-prepared armies clumsily
into the lair of the wolf.
And only zealous men
who stand steadfast
in the face of the enemy
will be etched
in German memory forever.
And it is up to you to decide
if you want to be remembered,
or disappear without a trace
like a pitiful grain
of sand into a desert
of insignificance.
To put it plainly...
get your shit together
and sort out your priorities.
You're ten, Jojo.
Start acting like it.
No.
Did you know?
She didn't tell me much...
only that she worked
with her friends
and your father was
somehow involved from afar.
No. He's fighting in the war.
She said he'll be home
as soon as the war's over.
She didn't want to tell you
anything for obvious reasons.
Because she hated me.
'Cause I'm a Nazi.
I'm the enemy.
She didn't want you
to know anything
that could get you in trouble.
But now I have nothing.
No one.
The last time I saw my parents
was at the station.
They were put on a train.
I ran.
Slowly found my way
back to the city.
A friend of my father's hid me.
Then another friend,
then friends of friends.
Until your mother took me in.
And so far, I'm still here.
But my...
my parents went to a place
you don't come back from.
What's the first thing
you'll do when you're free?
Dance.
♪ Everybody's gotta live ♪
♪ And everybody's gonna die ♪
♪ I think you know
the reason why ♪
♪ Sometimes
the goin' gets so good ♪
♪ Then again,
it gets pretty rough ♪
♪ But when I have you
in my arms, baby ♪
♪ You know I just can't,
I just can't get enough ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Everybody's gotta live ♪
♪ Yes, they do ♪
♪ And everybody's
gonna die ♪
♪ Everybody try to
have a, a good time ♪
♪ I think you know
the reason why ♪
♪ I feel like I've seen just
about a million sunsets ♪
♪ She said if you're with me,
I'll never go away ♪
♪ That's when I stopped
and I took another look
at my baby ♪
♪ She said if you're with me,
I'll never go away ♪
♪ Because ♪
♪ Everybody's gotta live ♪
♪ And everybody's
gonna die ♪
♪ Everybody's gotta live ♪
♪ Before you know
the reason why ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Everybody's gotta live ♪
That's it. That's it. Hurry.
Yorki?
Jojo!
Oh, God.
Jojo.
How I've missed you.
Sorry about your mama.
I cried for ages
when I heard what happened.
What's going on out here?
The Russians, Jojo.
They're coming.
And the Americans
from the other way.
And England and China
and Africa and India.
The whole world is coming.
Help me with this ammo.
- And how are we doing?
- Terribly.
Our only friends
are the Japanese.
And just between you and me,
they don't look very Aryan.
- Remember that Jew
I told you about?
- Oh, yeah.
I still have her.
She's basically
my girlfriend now.
Oh, good for you, Jojo.
A girlfriend.
But, you know, she's Jewish.
There are bigger things
to worry about
than Jews, Jojo.
There's Russians
somewhere out there.
They're worse than anyone.
I heard they eat babies
and have sex with dogs.
I mean, like, that's bad, right?
Sex with dogs?
Yeah.
The Englishmen do it, too.
We have to stop them
before they eat us
and screw all our dogs.
It's crazy.
And now Hitler's gone,
we're really on our own.
- What?
- You didn't hear?
He's dead.
He gave up
and blew his brains out.
No.
That's impossible.
Blew them out.
His brains.
Turns out he was hiding
a lot of stuff from us.
Doing some really bad things
behind everyone's backs.
I'm not sure
we chose the right side.
Okay. Come here. Okay.
See that American there?
Just go give him a hug.
Go! Run! Let's go!
Oh, Yorki. Yorki, great news.
You've just been promoted,
and you get your own pistol.
Just go and shoot anybody
who looks different to us.
- Okay.
Jojo, where's your uniform?
Here. Here,
put the jacket on
so they know not to shoot you.
We must kill everything
that we see.
For Hitler.
Die, devil scum!
Die!
Fall out!
Whoo! Ha!
Ja.
Come. This way.
They are here!
The Americans!
Come on.
- Stay on him.
- Behind you, Cap.
Over here. Come on, go!
I'll check him.
Hey, boys! Whoo-hoo!
Move the prisoners.
Keep the prisoners all in line.
Quickly. Quickly!
Hey! Hey!
What?
I-I don't understand.
Move! Move!
Get up, wretched dog.
Captain K.
Heya, kid.
Look at all this commotion, huh?
- What's happening?
- Hysteria, my friend.
We've come...
We've come to the end.
- Party's over.
- No, I'm not like them.
- Are you scared?
Don't be scared.
No. Please.
- Look at me.
- No. No.
I'm sorry about Rosie.
She was a good person.
An actual good person.
Okay?
Hey. It's okay, kid.
Shh, shh, shh.
I've been meaning
to tell you. I think
your book is really great.
Ja, I'm sorry
for laughing at it.
Very creative.
Come here,
let's take a look at you.
You look good.
You're okay, kid.
Now, go home. Look after
that sister of yours.
Okay?
Get away. Get away, Jew.
- Hey! What's going on?
- Get away!
- He's a Jew.
Shut up.
You know this Nazi?
- He helped us.
- No, I don't know
this dirty Jew.
No, no...
- Get away, Jew.
- Hey. Hey!
Shut your mouth, Nazi.
- No! No! No!
- Get out of here. Go home.
- No! Leave him alone!
- Go home!
No!
- Get off!
- Get out of here.
Go home!
Jojo?
Yorki!
Thank God.
I thought you were dead.
No. It seems like
I can never die.
I'm gonna go home
and see my mother.
I need a cuddle.
- Nothing makes
sense anymore.
- Ja, I know.
It's definitely not
a good time to be a Nazi.
Hey. So now the war's over,
at least your girlfriend
will be free.
She can leave now.
Something wrong?
I've got to go.
- Okay.
- Sorry.
Later!
Hi. I'm home.
What's going on out there?
- Out where?
- Outside, dummy.
Jojo, what's going on?
Is it safe to come out?
Jojo, is it safe?
Can I leave?
No.
You can't leave.
Why?
You have to stay here...
Who won?
with me.
Jojo, who won... who won the war?
We did.
Germany won the war.
I-I'm sorry.
"Dear Elsa.
"I know it's hard for you
at the moment...
"and I know
you feel like giving up.
"But you have to carry on.
"Me and your good friend, Jojo,
"have devised a plan
for you to escape.
"So, please listen to him.
"He's gonna help you
get out of there.
"And then you can
come live with me in Paris.
"And don't worry about Jojo.
"He'll be okay.
"See you in Paris.
Nathan."
- He's dead.
- Pardon?
Nathan.
He died last year.
Tuberculosis.
Well... that's weird.
Who wrote these?
Thank you, Jojo.
You have been so good to me.
Well, the thing is, I love you.
I know you think of me
as a younger brother,
which is fine,
and, um, you're too old anyway.
But...
Man, it's quite hot in here.
I love you, too.
- As a younger brother.
Look, me and fake Nathan
have found a way
for you to escape.
Maybe you can trust
a younger brother?
Maybe.
Okay, then.
Get your things together.
We're leaving.
Jojo Betzler.
Ten and a half years old.
Today,
just do what you can.
Where in the shit do you
think you're going, hmm?
- Out.
- Out? Oh, no, you don't.
No, we're gonna stay in here
and you're gonna tell me
exactly what's going on
with you and that thing
in the attic.
That "thing" is a girl.
- You're in love with her,
aren't you?
- Yes.
- Admit it.
- I just said yes.
I knew it!
Well, it's never gonna work out.
No. No, she's too old for you.
And you're ugly.
You know
she's gonna leave you.
You know that, don't you?
So, here's what's
gonna happen, you little shit.
You're gonna put this on, okay?
You're gonna forget about that
disgusting Jewy cow up there.
And you're gonna come
back to me, where you belong.
Right?
Put it on.
And then, we're gonna pretend
none of this ever happened.
You got it?
You're not gonna heil me?
Come on? For old time's sake?
- Heil me, little man.
- No.
- Heil me.
Give me a little heil.
Just a little heil. Please?
Fuck off, Hitler.
Come on.
Oh. Wait.
Ready?
Yeah.
Is it dangerous out there?
Extremely.
Yeah!
Whoo!
We made it.
Probably deserved that.
What do we do now?
♪ Du, könntest du schwimmen ♪
♪ Wie Delphine ♪
♪ Delphine es tun ♪
♪ Niemand gibt
uns eine Chance ♪
♪ Doch können wir siegen ♪
♪ Für immer und immer ♪
♪ Und wir sind dann Helden ♪
♪ Für einen Tag ♪
♪ Ich ♪
♪ Ich bin dann König ♪
♪ Und du ♪
♪ Du Königin ♪
♪ Obwohl sie
unschlagbar scheinen ♪
♪ Werden wir Helden ♪
♪ Für einen Tag ♪
♪ Wir sind dann wir ♪
♪ An diesem Tag ♪
♪ Ich ♪
♪ Ich glaubte zu träumen ♪
♪ Zu träumen ♪
♪ Die Mauer ♪
♪ Im Rücken war kalt ♪
♪ So kalt ♪
♪ Schüsse ♪
♪ Reißen die Luft ♪
♪ Reißen
die Luft ♪
♪ Doch wir küssen ♪
♪ Als ob nichts geschieht ♪
♪ Nichts geschieht ♪
♪ Und die Scham ♪
♪ Fiel auf ihrer Seite ♪
♪ Oh, wir können sie schlagen ♪
♪ Für alle Zeiten ♪
♪ Dann sind wir Helden ♪
♪ Für diesen Tag ♪